A Guide to the Lewis W. Hackett Papers FA043
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Diaries, 1910-1962; 2
  - Manuscripts - Travel in Europe, January 1-August 8, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - 1 Book - South America, 1948 (Box 12, Folder A)
  - 1 Book - South America, U.S., Europe, 1949 (Box 12, Folder B)
  - 1 Book - Travel in Canada, Europe, August 24, 1960-May 18, 1961 (Box 12, Folder C)
  - 7 Books - "Daily Reminder" - U.S. and Miscellaneous Travel, 1956-1962 (Box 13, Folder A)
- Speeches, Manuscripts and Reprints, 1920-1961; 3
  Of the 33 speeches collected here, 19 were given in South America between 1940 and 1949. Most of those in Spanish or Portuguese have been translated. The subjects are epidemiology, current trends in public health, and general observations of South America. One talk includes an excellent explanation of the Foundation's aims and policies. There are also four manuscript drafts of journal articles and 32 reprints of other articles, mostly on malaria. These are arranged alphabetically by title. Included are three chapters he contributed to "Malariology," by Mark F. Boyd (2v., Saunders, 1949); his "Encyclopedia Britannica" entry on tropical medicine; and three feature stories for "Brazilian American" magazine in 1922.
  The speeches in this series are arranged chronologically. They are followed by manuscript drafts of journal articles and reprints of articles. The reprints are arranged alphabetically by title. The series ends with other pieces authored by Hackett.
  - Remarks at a Ceremony on the Occasion of the Stazione Sperimentale per la Lotta Antimalarica Becoming Part of the Public Health Administration in Italy, November 20, 1934 (Box 14, Folder 159)
    English.
  - Remarks at a Rotary Club Luncheon, Buenos Aires, March 26, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 160)
    Spanish.
  - Speech Before the "Club de Mjujeres," Buenos Aires, [April 1, 1941] (Box 14, Folder 161)
    May be speech given on this date before "American" Women's Club, mentioned in diary. Spanish.
  - Speech on the Modern Orientation of Public Health, December 17, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 162)
    Given before medical personnel of Health Department, Santiago, Chile. English.
  - "The Modern Trend in Public Health", [June 10, 1944] (Box 14, Folder 163)
    Paper probably read before the medical society in Tucuman, Argentina. English and Spanish.
  - Remarks at the Inauguration of the School of Public Health, Santiago, Chile, May 8, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Introduction of Dr. Carlos Alberto Alvarado, June 19, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 165)
    Alvarado received in Buenos Aires an honorary degree from the University of Portland. English and Spanish.
  - "A Case in Epidemiology", September 18, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    Speech before the Sociedad Cientifica Argentina. Spanish and English.
  - "The Rockefeller Foundation and the Modern Concept of Public Health", [August 2, 1946] (Box 14, Folder 167)
    Read before the Instituto de Conferencias Populares under the auspices of "La Prensa," Buenos Aires. English. Excellent explanation of Rockefeller Foundation general policy.
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Series 6.4, Clippings.
  - "Introduccion a la Epidemiologia", [June 16, 1947] (Box 14, Folder 168)
    Given in Tucuman, Argentina; probably a lecture at the Universidad Nacional de Tucuman, Escuela de Higiene, a post-graduate course in hygiene and regional medicine. Spanish and English.
  - "La Epidemiologia del Paludismo", [June 17, 1947] (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - "Epidemiologia General: Epidemiologia de la Fiebre Amarilla", [June 18, 1947] (Box 14, Folder 170)
  - "Salud Publica, Hoy y Manana", [September 29, 1947] (Box 14, Folder 171)
    Written by Lewis W. Hackett to be given by Dr. F. L. Soper on 9/29 or 9/30/47 at the Faculty of Medicine, Buenos Aires, but the occasion was cancelled. English.
  - Two Tropical Diseases of America", May 8, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 172)
    CBS radio broadcast, "Adventures in Science" series. English.
  - Untitled Speech, [May 17, 1948] (Box 14, Folder 173)
    Speech given at a banquet at the International Congress on Tropical Medicine and Malaria, Washington, D.C. Handwritten. English.
  - "Public Health, Today and Tomorrow", June 12, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 174)
    Given in La Plata, Argentina, before the Ministry of Health. Rewrite of "Salud Publica, Hoy y Manana." Spanish and English.
  - "The South American Scene", [November 13, 1948] (Box 14, Folder 175)
    Given before the Royal Canadian Institute, Toronto. English.
  - "Report on South America", [March 1949] (Box 14, Folder 176)
    Read before the "Round Table group" in Buenos Aires. English.
  - Remarks at the Unveiling of a Plaque Commemorating the First Rockefeller Foundation Work in Brazil in Minas Gerais, May 3, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 177)
    English and Portuguese. With photograph.
  - Remarks at the Inauguration of the Instituto de Malaria in Rio de Janiero, [May 7, 1949] (Box 14, Folder 178)
    English and Portuguese.
  - "Paper", [August 31, 1949] (Box 14, Folder 179)
    Read at the American Club, Buenos Aires. Similar to "Report on South America," Folder 176. English.
  - Address at Farewell Banquet Given by Argentine Doctors in Buenos Aires, [September 12, 1949] (Box 14, Folder 180)
    English and Spanish. With guest list and introduction in Spanish by Dr. Bernardo Houssay.
  - Remarks on Receiving Medal of Officer of the Order of Merit "Bernardo O'Higgins," in Chile, September 19, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 181)
    With introduction by Dr. Hernan Romero. Both Spanish.
    See also Subseries 6.4, Clippings.
  - Remarks at a Luncheon in Lewis W. Hackett's Honor at the Rockefeller Foundation New York Office, November 2, 1949 (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - "Public Health Reminiscences", 1952 (Box 14, Folder 183)
    (Title origin uncertain.) Remarks at a dinner of the Delta Omega Society, University of California. English.
  - Speech on the Role of Insecticides, [1952] (Box 14, Folder 184)
    Speech given at the 20th Annual Conference of the California Mosquito Control Association. English.
  - "The International Health Movement", [ca. October 24, 1953] (Box 14, Folder 185)
    Given before the Rotary Club in California as part of United Nations Week observance. English.
  - Remarks on Acceptance of the Walter Reed Medal from the American Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene, [November 14, 1953] (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - "A Pilot Experiment in International Collaboration", February 17, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 187)
    Given at a Pan American Medical Association dinner; a survey of Rockefeller Foundation work in public health in South America. English.
  - "Tropical Palimpsest", October 26, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    Given before the Harvard Club; on tropical medicine and related topics. English.
  - Introduction of Dr. William Hay Taliaferro at a Meeting of the American Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene in Boston, November 1955 (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Typewritten Manuscripts (Box 14, Folder 190)
    Hackett, L. W. and M. A. Barber. "Notes on the 'maculipennis' races of Russia." Intended publication unknown, [c.1934]. Revised draft with pencil notes appended.
    Hackett, L. W. and M. A. Barber. "Notes on varieties of A. 'maculipennis' in the U.S.S.R." Moscow, Journal of Medical Parasitology, October, 1934. First and final drafts.
    Hackett, L. W. "Recent advances in medicine and public health." Buenos Aires, Bulletin of the American Chamber of Commerce, 1946. Final draft.
    Hackett, L. W. "Amazonas, old and new." Cambridge, Harvard Medical Alumni Bulletin, [March] 1949. Final draft.
  - Speech on the Ports of Brazil, with Notes, [1920-1925] (Box 15, Folder 191)
    English. One page of notes is dated December 20, 1919. A letter from Lewis W. Hackett to Dr. G. K. Strode dated January 17, 1925 (in Subseries 1.1) refers to a lecture probably based partly on these notes.
  - "Malaria Control Through Anti-Mosquito Measures", [1929] (Box 15, Folder 192)
    No other identification. Includes transcript of remarks by a Col. James (probably Col. S. P. James, malariologist).
  - Reprints of Chapters Contributed by Lewis W. Hackett to "Malariology," by Mark F. Boyd (Box 15, Folder 193)
    "28. Distribution of malaria." "32. Conspectus of malaria incidence in northern Europe, the Mediterranean region and the near east." "65. Malaria control in the palearctic region." With Shabsei Moshkovski.
  - Reprints (Box 15, Folder 194)
    Putnam, Persis and Lewis W. Hackett. "An appraisal of malaria reduction in Albania, 1919-1938." Journal of the National Malaria Society, V. 6, No. 2, June, 1947.
    Putnam, Persis and Lewis W. Hackett. "An appraisal of the malaria endemic in protected and comparison areas of Sardinia in the years 1925-1934." Journal of the National Malaria Society, V. 5, No. 1, March, 1946.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Biological factors in malaria control." American Journal of Tropical Medicine, V. 16, No. 3, May, 1936.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Differences in the habits of anophelines which transmit malaria in America, in Europe and in the far east." Southern Medical Journal, V. XXII, No. 4, April, 1929.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "The disappearance of malaria in Europe and the United States." Rivista di Parassitologia, V. XIII, No. 1, January, 1952.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "The importance and uses of Paris green (copper aceto arsenite) as an 'anopheles' larvacide." First International Congress on Malaria, October 4-6, Rome, Italy (1925).
    Bates, Marston and Hackett, Lewis W. "The laboratory for mosquito research in Albania." Transaction of the Third International Congress of Tropical Medicine and Malaria, 1938, V. II.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Malaria and the community." American Association for the Advancement of Science, Publication No. 15, undated.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "The malaria of the Andean region of South America." Revista del Instituto de Salubridad y Enfermedades Tropicales, V. VI, no. 4, December, 1945.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "La medicion del bazo en la malaria." Revista de Medicina Experimental, V. II, No. 4, 1943.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Methodes biologiques de lutte antipaludeenne." Rivista di Malariologia, Section I, Suppl. to No. 6, 1935.
    Hackett, Lewis W. and A. Missiroli. "The natural disappearance of malaria in certain regions of Europe." American Journal of Hygiene, V. XIII, No. 1, January, 1931.
    Hackett, Lewis W. and D. J. Lewis. "A new variety of 'Anopheles maculipennis' in Southern Europe." Rivista di Malariologia, Section I, No. 5, 1935.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Once upon a time; presidential address." American Journal of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene, V. IX, No. 2, March, 1960.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "The present status of our knowledge of the sub-species of 'Anopheles maculipennis'." Transactions of the Royal Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene, V. XXVIII, No. 2, August, 1934.
  - Reprints and Encyclopedia Britannica Article (Box 15, Folder 195)
    Hackett, Lewis W. et al. "The present use of naturalistic measures in the control of malaria." Quarterly Bulletin of the Health Organization of the League of Nations, no date. (after Oct. 1937).
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Un problema en epidemiologia." Anales de la Sociedad Cientifica Argentina, V. CXL, November, 1945.
    Missiroli, A., Lewis W. Hackett and E. Martini. "Le razze di 'Anopheles maculipennis' e la loro importanza mella distribuzione della malaria in alcune regioni d'Europa." Rivista di Malariologia, No. 1, 1933.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Recent additions to our knowledge of 'Anopheles maculipennis' races." Quarterly Bulletin of the Health Organization of the League of Nations, V. VI, Extract No. 1, no date.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Recent findings bearing on the epidemiology of malaria in Europe." Medical Parasitology and Parasitic Diseases, V. 4, No. 1-2, (1935).
    Missiroli, A. and Lewis W. Hackett. "La regressione spontanea della malaria in alcune regioni d'Italia." Rivista di Malariologia, Fascicule 2, 1927.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Spleen measurement in malaria." Journal of the National Malaria Society, V. III, No. 2, 1944.
    Hackett, Lewis W. and Marston Bates. "Swarming of the males of certain European anophelines in captivity." Nature, V. 138, p. 506, September 19, 1936.
    Hackett, Lewis W. and A. Missiroli. "Les varietes d'anopheles maculipennis et leur relation avec la distribution du paludisme en Europe." Medicina de los Paises Calidos, No. 1, January, 1935.
    Hackett, Lewis W. and A. Missiroli. "The varieties of 'Anopheles maculipennis' and their relation to the distribution of malaria in Europe." Rivista di Malariologia, Section I, No. 1, 1935.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Tropical medicine." Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1961.
  - "Brazilian American" Articles (Box 15, Folder 196)
    Hackett, Lewis W. "To Iguassu on business." Brazilian American, V. 5, No. 115, January 7, 1922. (two copies)
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Selling public health in Brazil." Brazilian American, V. 5, No. 123, March 4, 1922.
    Hackett, Lewis W. "Do you know Itatiaya?" Brazilian American, V. 6, No. 140, July 1, 1922. (This issue also contains an article on "Rockefeller Commission" work in Bahia.)
- Reports, 1921-1948; 4
  This series consists of annual, semi-annual, quarterly, and miscellaneous reports, mostly of the "Stazione Sperimentale per la Lotta Antimalarica" in Italy and the Rio de la Plata and Andean Region in South America.
  - 7 Books - Stazione Sperimentale per la Lotta Antimalarica, 1925-1930 (Box 16, Folder A)
  - 9 Books - Stazione Sperimentale per la Lotta Antimalarica, 1931-1934 (Box 17, Folder B)
  - 11 Books - Stazione Sperimentale per la Lotta Antimalarica, 1935-1939 (Box 18, Folder C)
  - 9 Books - International Health Division (IHD) Rio de la Plata and Andean Region, 1941-1948 (Box 19, Folder D)
  - 9 Books - Miscellaneous Reports, 1921-1940 (Box 20, Folder E)
- Malaria Data, Egypt, 1938-1940; 5
  This series contains records of spleen and blood examinations of children and adults in a number of Egyptian villages, entered in five ledger books and three envelopes of loose-leaf notebook pages.
  - Malaria Data (Box 20, Folder 197)
    1 envelope of loose-leaf notebook pages, "Malaria data on Mit Salsil" - undated.
    1 envelope of loose-leaf notebook pages, "Malaria data on Nawa" - undated.
    1 envelope of loose-leaf notebook pages, "Malaria data on Tida" - undated.
  - Loose Notes Found in Above Books (oversize), 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 198)
  - 5 Books - Records of Spleen and Blood Examinations, 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder A)
- Miscellaneous, 1891-1962; 6
  Series 6 is divided into 8 subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Address, Appointment, and Memo Books
  Subseries 2 - Biographical Information
  Subseries 3 - Certificates, Diplomas, Etc.
  Subseries 4 - Clippings
  Subseries 5 - Memorabilia
  Subseries 6 - Miscellaneous Notes and Writings
  Subseries 7 - Miscellany
  Subseries 8 - Oversize Items from Series 6.1 through Series 6.7
  - Miscellaneous - Address, Appointment, and Memo Books, 1951-1962; 1
    This subseries contains two address books, two appointment books for 1951-1952 containing a few diary-type notations, and a group of pocket memo books from 1951 through March 1962, with reminders, telephone numbers, quotations, etc., mostly of a personal nature. This subseries contains little of value.
    - 23 Monthly Pocket Memo Books, January 1951-December 1952 (Box 22, Folder 199)
      Lacking April 1951.
    - 24 Monthly Pocket Memo Books, January 1953-December 1954 (Box 22, Folder 200)
    - 24 Monthly Pocket Memo Books, January 1955-December 1956 (Box 22, Folder 201)
    - 24 Monthly Pocket Memo Books, January 1957-December 1958 (Box 22, Folder 202)
    - 24 Monthly Pocket Memo Books, January 1959-December 1960 (Box 22, Folder 203)
    - 15 Monthly Pocket Memo Books, January 1961-March 1962 (Box 22, Folder 204)
    - 2 Loose Pages of Brazilian Addresses (Box 22, Folder 205)
    - 2 Books - Addresses (Box 22, Folder A)
    - 2 Books - Appointments, 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder B)
  - Miscellaneous - Biographical Information, 2
    This subseries consists of miscellaneous biographical sketches, notes, and curriculum vitae. One includes a list of published articles, probably incomplete.
    - Biographical Sketches and Curriculum Vitae (Box 23, Folder 206)
  - Miscellaneous - Certificates, Diplomas, Etc., 1905-1961; 3
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the name of the issuing body.
    - Miscellaneous Certificates, Diplomas, Etc., 1905-1961 (Box 23, Folder 207)
      Separated Materials
      See also oversize material in Series 6.8.
    - Certificates, Diplomas, Etc. (Box 23A, Folder 207A)
  - Miscellaneous - Clippings, 1902-1962; 4
    This subseries contains clippings about Dr. Hackett and/or the Rockefeller Foundation (mostly in Portuguese or Spanish), reviews of his book, and miscellaneous clippings, and contains little of value.
    This subseries is arranged by type of material, and thereunder chronologically.
    - Items About Dr. Hackett or Rockefeller Foundation-Related Items, 1914-1962 (Box 23, Folder 208)
    - Book Reviews, 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Miscellaneous Items, 1902-1962, undated (Box 23, Folder 210)
      See also Series 6.8 for oversize clippings.
  - Miscellaneous - Memorabilia, 1902-1961; 5
    This subseries contains menus, programs, invitations, tickets, calling cards, blank forms, souvenirs, etc. Items of more than routine interest are a miniature hatchet pin apparently acquired from Carrie Nation, leaflets dropped from Italian war planes on Albania, and a wallet containing a variety of identity cards, licenses, etc.
    This subseries is divided into 3 sections: 1) items related to Harvard, 2) professionally-related items, and 3) miscellaneous. It is arranged chronologically thereunder.
    - Items Related to Harvard, 1902-1941 (Box 23, Folder 211)
    - Professionally-Related Items, Undated & 1915-1949 (Box 23, Folder 212)
    - Miscellaneous Items, Undated & 1891-1929 (Box 23, Folder 213)
    - Miscellaneous Items, Undated & 1930-1961 (Box 23, Folder 214)
    - Wallet with Identity Cards, etc. & Passports (Box 23, Folder 215)
      See also Series 6.8 for oversize memorabilia.
  - Miscellaneous - Miscellaneous Notes and Writings, 1910-1958, n.d.; 6
    This subseries consists of notes and short pieces of prose and verse on a variety of subjects entered on loose cards and sheets or in notebooks.
    - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated & 1924-1958 (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - "Memphis Article" (on Distribution of Malaria in Egypt), undated (Box 23, Folder 217)
    - Miscellaneous Writings, Undated & 1923-1946 (Box 23, Folder 218)
    - 7 Notebooks - Miscellaneous Notes, Undated & 1910-1961 (Box 24, Folder A)
      See also Series 6.8 for oversize miscellaneous notes.
  - Miscellaneous - Miscellany, 7
    This subseries contains a few letters, verses, speeches, pamphlets, etc. by others or of unknown authorship and/or lacking apparent connection to Dr. Hackett or his work.
    - Letters, Miscellaneous Writings, Undated & 1901-1949 (Box 25, Folder 219)
    - Memoranda, Verse, Undated & 1922-1950 (Box 25, Folder 220)
    - Pamphlets, Institutional Publications, 1923-1939 (Box 25, Folder 221)
    - Harvard Class Album, 1905 (Box 25, Folder 222)
  - Miscellaneous - Oversize Items from Series 6.1 through Series 6.7, 8
    This subseries contains clippings, memorabilia, and notes of little research value.
    - Oversize Clippings and Memorabilia, 1909-1940, undated (Box 26, Folder 223)
    - Oversize Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 26, Folder 224)
- Lewis W. Hackett Photographs, Negatives, and Slides, 1914-1949; 1071; 41 box(es)
  File Plan note
  P/1071
  The Lewis W. Hackett Photograph Collection spans the period 1885-1962. The majority of the contents in this collection are photographs taken by Dr. Hackett during his tenure with the International Health Division/Board. Also, included in this collection are pictures of the Hackett family and home, Lewis Hackett as a child, and documentation of various ailments and diseases throughout the world. Lewis W. Hackett spent much of his career in South America and Eastern Europe, as is evidenced by the volume of photographs from these regions. The collection, however, is not limited to these regions, as nearly all of the continents are represented in the extensive visual collection. The photograph collection is housed in 41 boxes and contains photographs, negatives, slides, and post cards. Dr. Hackett was an avid and competent photographer, and varied subjects from most of the countries in which Dr. Hackett worked or traveled are represented.
  Photographs
  - Photographs, 1
    - Photographs -- Loose Photographs, 1.1
      This subseries has been sorted geographically and foldered either by country or region.
      - Albania (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Albania (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Albania (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Albania (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Balkans (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Folder contains Bulgaria, Croatia, Dalmatia, Yugoslavia.
      - Greece/Crete (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Russia (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Britain (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Czechoslovakia (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - France (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Germany (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Italy (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Italy (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Italy (Box 2, Folder 14)
        Rome, Sicily
      - Ireland (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Portugal (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Scotland (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Spain (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Switzerland (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Ceylon (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Indonesia (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Malaya (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Philippines (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Siam (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Sumatra (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - India (Box 3, Folder 26)
        Folder contains Madras, Mysore, Bombay.
      - Argentina (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Bolivia (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Brazil (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Brazil (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Brazil (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - British Guyana (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Chile (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Columbia (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Mexico (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Mexico (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Panama (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Paraguay (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Peru (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Uruguay (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Venezuela (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Latin America (Box 4, Folder 42)
        Contains miscellaneous materials from Latin America
      - Egypt (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Palestine (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Middle East (Box 5, Folder 45)
        Folder contains Bethlehem, Jericho, Jordan, Jerusalem.
      - Turkey (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - United States (Box 6, Folder 47)
        Folder includes California, Georgia, Mississippi
      - Science/Medicine (Box 6, Folder 48)
        Folder contains images of diseases.
      - Science/Medicine (Box 6, Folder 49)
        Folder contains images of mosquitoes and other specimens.
      - Other Format (Box 7, Folder 50)
        Folder contains group photo, Latin America, all persons identified.
      - Harvard Medical School Class of 1912 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Oversize Print - India (Box 7, Folder 52)
        Enlarged photo of Allahabad, India.
      - Print Material (Box 7, Folder 53)
        Folder contains miscellaneous printed materials, correspondence, lists, broadside.
      - Oversize Prints (Box 7, Folder 54)
        Folder contains prints not taken by Lewis W. Hackett.
      - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 55)
        Unidentified small format photographs
      - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 59)
        Unidentified medium format photographs
      - Unidentified (Box 8, Folder 60)
        Unidentified large format photographs
      - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 61)